cutmirchi.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy | Cutmirchi.com

---  

_**What information do we collect? :**_  

  * Cut Mirchi currently not asking any signup to user to submit their links. Now it is open to all users. Every Link will be reviewed before approval. 

  * We record IP address, Cookie information for providing better services. 

_**What do we use your information for? :**_  

  * Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways 

  * * To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

  * * To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

_**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?:**_  

  * We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. 

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

_**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements : **_  

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit[ http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

_**Third party links**_  

  * Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.   

  * Online Privacy Policy Only   

  * Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms   

  * If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
